(Sheldon:)I sent out a very emphatic Twitter.
I changed my Facebook status to "Sheldon
wishes Penny would leave him alone."
(Sheldon:)I don't know what else to do.
(Leonard:)Well, what am I supposed to do?
(Sheldon:)If you don't figure something out,
I warn you...
(Sheldon:)...I shall become very difficult
to live with.
(Leonard:)You mean, up until now we've been
experiencing the happy fun-time Sheldon?
(Sheldon:)- Yes.
- I'll go talk to her.
(Penny:)No, Fritz, I need you on my flank.
(Penny:)No, I don't know German.
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
- Hey, Penny?
- Busy.
(Leonard:)Yeah, I see that.
Shouldn't you be at work?
(Penny:)I don't work on Mondays.
(Leonard:)It's Thursday.
(Leonard:)- Listen, Penny...
- Ugh. Queen Penelope AFK. What?
Okay. Uh...
(Leonard:)Here's the thing.
(Leonard:)Um, sometimes people, good people,
you know, they start playing these games.